hi folks its Matt again and now we're
嗨，大家好，Matt，现在我们
ready to start solving games and making
准备开始解决游戏和制作
some predictions of how people will play
关于人们如何玩的一些预测
in different settings and so we're
在不同的设置中，所以我们
talking right now about Nash equilibrium
现在谈论纳什均衡
which is one probably the most basic and
这可能是最基本的
standard solution concept of all in all
全部的标准解决方案概念
of game theory it's named after John
博弈论的名字，以约翰命名
Nash who was a mathematician at
纳什（Nash）是数学家
Princeton and actually some years back
普林斯顿，实际上几年前
won the Nobel Prize for his work on this
他在这方面的工作获得了诺贝尔奖
subject and it's a very basic and
主题，这是一个非常基本的
fundamental concept and in order to sort
基本概念和排序
of motivate it let's let's start by just
激励它，让我们从一开始就开始
talking through some a particular game
通过特定游戏进行交谈
that was described and invented by
被描述和发明的
another famous person so this is John
另一个名人，所以这是约翰
Kane John Maynard Keynes beauty contest
凯恩·约翰·梅纳德·凯恩斯选美大赛
game so what's the idea here so let's
游戏，这是什么主意，让我们
let's think of a basic situation that
让我们考虑一个基本情况
you might be interested in and this was
您可能对此感兴趣，这是
one that Keynes described in some detail
凯恩斯对此进行了详细描述
so the idea was you have a stock you're
所以想法是你有一只股票
holding on to it and the stock price is
坚持下去，股价就是
rising that's great you're an investor
上升那太好了，您是投资者
you're trying to make profits off of
你试图从中获利
your your stock holdings and you begin
您的库存量，然后开始
to believe that maybe the stock is too
相信也许股票也是如此
high to be justified by the value of the
高要由价值来证明
company so you're thinking that it's
公司，所以您认为这是
possible that this stock is overvalued
这只股票可能被高估了
maybe there's a bubble in the market and
也许市场上有泡沫，
you're starting to think about selling
您开始考虑出售
okay well you'd like to sell it but
好吧，你想卖掉它，但是
you'd like to wait until the price is at
您想等到价格在
its peak right so you'd want to wait
它的峰值合适，所以您想等待
until the price was just where it's
直到价格刚好在
going to hit its maximum before you sold
在您卖出之前将达到最高
so you wanted to get out of the market
所以你想退出市场
just before the other investors do so
就在其他投资者这样做之前
this is a game where now you have to
这是一个游戏，现在您必须
predict what other people think about
预测别人的想法
the stock price and and what they're
股票价格以及它们的含义
going to do and when they want to get
去做，什么时候想得到
out so how will they act how should you
出来，他们将如何行动，你应该如何
respond to that so this is the basic
对此做出回应，这是最基本的
ingredients of Nash equilibrium are
纳什均衡的成分是
going to be having some prediction of
会有一些预测
what other players are doing and then
其他玩家在做什么，然后
choosing the optimal strategy in
选择最佳策略
response to that so these are they're
回应，所以这些是
going to be two key ingredients that we
将成为我们的两个关键要素
have so there's a very stylized version
有一个非常程式化的版本
of this which is known as the the Keynes
这就是凯恩斯
beauty contest game where did it come
选美比赛是哪里来的
from
从
actually Keynes described the there was
实际上凯恩斯描述了
a newspaper in the in England that had a
英格兰的一家报纸
contest where players had to guess which
比赛中玩家必须猜测哪个
picture of several women other readers
其他读者的几个女人的照片
would think was the the the most
会认为是最
attractive one so it wasn't to guess
有吸引力的一个，所以不用猜测
what you thought but what you thought
你在想什么，但你在想什么
other people were thinking so Keynes
其他人在想，所以凯恩斯
likened investing to this you it's not
比作投资，这不是
only what you think of this the stock
只有您对此的看法
but what you think other people are
但是你认为别人是什么
thinking about the stock that's
考虑那只股票
important and driving your decisions
重要并推动您的决策
okay so this now is represented by a
好吧，现在以
very simple game that is is played by
玩的非常简单的游戏
many people so what's this game look
很多人，所以这个游戏看起来像什么
like each person gets to name an integer
就像每个人都用一个整数命名
between 1 and 100 ok so you get to pick
在1到100 ok之间，所以您可以选择
a number between 1 and 100 s to be an
1到100秒之间的数字是一个
integer so 1 2 3 etc players are going
整数，所以1 2 3等玩家进行
to move simultaneously and the player
与玩家同时移动
who names the integer that's closest to
谁命名最接近的整数
two-thirds of the average integer wins a
平均整数的三分之二赢得
prize and the other players get nothing
奖，其他玩家一无所获
so to win this game you have to get you
所以要赢得这场比赛，你必须让你
have to guess the average and then 2/3
必须猜测平均值，然后再2/3
of it right so you want to be right at
它是正确的，所以你想在正确
2/3 of whatever the average guess is so
平均猜测的2/3
a little bit below the average guess if
比平均猜测低一点
there's two people that happen to hit
有两个人碰巧
the same integer that it's the the right
正确的整数
one then ties are going to be broken
一个然后领带将被打破
uniformly at random so we'll just flip a
均匀地随机分布，所以我们只需要翻转一个
coin or if there's three people will
硬币，或者如果有三个人
roll a dice a three-sided die etc okay
掷骰子，三面骰子等
so how would you play this game you have
所以你会怎么玩这个游戏
to think about what other players are
考虑其他玩家
going to do and then forecast what you
去做，然后预测你
think the best integer is in a response
认为最好的整数在响应中
to that
那个